home: Belarus, Minsk

phone/viber: +375(29) 5574550 e-mail: <u>ivanenko.igor.88@gmail.com</u>

skype: <u>Igor Iv</u> telegram: <u>@ki11roy</u> LinkedIn: <u>Igor Ivanenko</u>



ABOUT ME:

I'm a Salesforce developer. Started work in this technology in 2018 year and keep working. Committed to excellence, self-motivator, fast-learner and a prudent developer with strong problem-solving skills and communication skills. Ability to learn the latest technologies fast and keep up in a fast-paced environment.

Enthusiastic and capable team player; willing to listen, facilitate, and contribute; likes to exchange knowledge with other team members; proven ability to work independently as well as a part of an integrated team.

Strong logical, analytical, and problem-solving skills, good communication skills; detail and customer-oriented; excellent ability to adapt fast to new software technologies and tools.

OBJECTIVE:

Looking for new opportunities to work in modern companies in the new teams on interesting projects as a developer.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS:

Programming Language: Apex, Java

Technologies: Sales Cloud, Service Cloud, LWC, Aura components, Approval Processes,

Sharing/Security models, Reports, Dashboards, Sites/Communities, Profiles, Migration tools, Rest/SOAP api, Bulk api, SFDX, Workflow/Validation

rules/Flow/Process Builder, Lightning / Visualfore, Servlet, JSP

APEX: SOQL/SOSL/DML operations, Async Apex, Schedulers, Dynamic Apex,

REST services, Triggers, Interfaces, Future Calls, Batch jobs

Web: JS / HTML / CSS / XML / jQuery / Tomcat

Frameworks: NodeJS / Angular / Spring / Hibernate *Test Tools*: JUnit / TestNG / DbUnit / Dev Console

DB Languages: SOQL / SOSL / SQL

Other: Git / OOP / Design Patterns / MySQL / Maven / GitHub / GitLab

Development Tools: IntelliJ IDEA, Visual Studio Code

English: B2 (intermediate)

SALESFORCE CERTIFICATES:

Salesforce App Builder Salesforce Platform Developer I

PROJECTS:

→ The Client is a company working in the consulting industry, which offers a service for tracking KPI. The service can set tasks for the entire company development avenues, and evaluate the performance of each task. The main challenge of the projects was to build a developing process based on SFDX. Within the project, the team created data architecture, developed new functionality from scratch based on LWC components, using standard LWC components.

- → Bullhorn is the global leader in CRM and operations software for the recruitment industry. As of 2019, the company reported more than 11,000 customers in more than 150 countries. Headquartered in Boston, with offices around the world, Bullhorn is founder-led and employs more than 950 people globally. The main challenge of the project was to distribute investigation results between development teams by creating tickets. The team also suggested several implementations based on best practices for optimizing product performance. Also, the challenge of the project was to develop Lightning components to replace Visualforce pages and components, and expand the functionality of the Connexys package. The goal was to streamline the features of the development process and grow the client base. Within the project, the team analyzed the existing functionality and provided the most efficient solution. The team also created new scratch orgs for testing and developing purposes.
- → EverFX global trading company that provides their client trading features. The main challenge was creating a CRM system for onboarding clients, affiliates and IB. Implement some integrations with other systems that include payments, client areas, managing and checking systems.

EDUCATION:

JetBI

Salesforce courses (1 month / 2018)

VRP Consulting

Salesforce courses (3 month / 2018)

itstart.by

Individual training at school of programming «ITstart» under the leadership of Pavel Veinik (01.2018-04.2018)

BNTU "Institute for Advanced Training and Retraining of Personnel", Minsk (2012-2014)

Physics Faculty

Chair: physics and informatics

BPSU n.a. M. Tank, Minsk (2007-2012)

EXPERIENCE:

iTech ART

Salesforce Developer (2020-)

VRP Consulting

Salesforce Developer (2018-2020)

Evrotorg

Software Support Specialist (2014-2018)

High School

System administrator/teacher (2011-2014)

freelance

Work with vector graphics